https://www.gtc.ox.ac.uk/policies/

Home > PoliciesPoliciesBelow you will find our key policies in PDF format:Charter & Statutes Code of Conduct College Regulations Equal Opportunities Policy Equality & Diversity Annual Report Events Guidelines and Policies Financial Regulations Free Speech Statement Freedom of Information Publication Scheme Harassment Policy Safeguarding Policy Student Concerns and Complaints Student Handbook 2019-20 Use of Controlled Substances and Legal HighsData ProtectionPersonal data collected and/or used by Green Templeton College is held in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):Privacy Notice for Students Data Register for StudentsPrivacy Notice for Student Applicants Data Register for Student ApplicantsPrivacy Notice for Alumni, Donors and Supporters Data Register for Alumni, Donors and SupportersPrivacy Notice for Fellows, Common Room Members and Research Associates Data Register for Fellows, Common Room Members and Research AssociatesPrivacy Notice for Staff Data Register for StaffPrivacy Notice for Archives Data Register for ArchivesPrivacy Notice for Conference and Events Data Register for Conference and EventsOther college policies relating to data management:CCTV Code of Practice Data Protection Policy Information Security Policy Cookie StatementThe College’s Data Protection Officer manages requests for personal data and other rights under GDPR:Kirsty Taylor Green Templeton College 43 Woodstock Road Oxford OX2 6HG +44 (0)1865 284596 dp@gtc.ox.ac.ukWe use cookies on this site to improve user experience. By clicking “ACCEPT” or accessing our site you consent to the use of cookies unless you have disabled them.AcceptDetails
